Guide to the Papers of Milo Guthrie, 1966-1987 RL.00488
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Milo Guthrie papers
1962-1987
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Guthrie, Milo
RL.00488
20.2 Linear Feet
circa 15,150 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The papers of Milo Guthrie were donated to the Duke University Library from 1980-1987 by Guthrie.
Biographical Note
Milo Guthrie is a long-time peace activist in Tennessee and North Carolina. A native of North Carolina, Guthrie lived in rural Cannon County, Tenn., for over ten years where he raised goats and was employed as a printer and commercial artist in Murfreesboro. Guthrie was an independent candidate for the Tennessee State House of Representatives in 1982 and a write-in candidate for Congress for Tennessee's Sixth Congressional District in 1984.
Guthrie has been an active supporter of the independent third party movement since the early 1970s. He served on the Executive Committee of the Peoples Party, as Parliamentarian of the California Peace and Freedom Party (PFP) State Convention, and on the PFP campaign of Gayle Justice in 1974. In 1980, Guthrie attended the founding convention of the Citizens Party as a delegate from Tennessee. He also served as state coordinator for the Presidential campaign of Socialist Party candidate David McReynolds.
Guthrie is a member of numerous political organizations including the Socialist Party, National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL), and the War Resisters League. (Taken from biography written by Guthrie for congressional campaign.)
Collection Overview
The Milo Guthrie Papers consist mainly of periodicals and printed materials produced by American politically left organizations and document a range of issues including civil rights, feminism, environmental defense, nuclear freeze and disarmament, gay and lesbian rights, Latin American and Puerto Rican politics, labor issues, and various political parties and candidates, particularly the Socialist Party. Included is a small amount of original material, primarily correspondence with members of various organizations concerning support for issues and activities. Much of this is directly related to the political campaigns of independent party candidates as well as Guthrie's own political campaigns in Tennessee in 1982 and 1984.
While the collection provides a concentrated wealth of information on a wide range of political and social issues during a time of significant political activity from the left, there is relatively little documentation of Guthrie's involvement with most of the groups represented in the collection's periodicals and printed materials. Scattered notes on flyers and form letters show that he was involved in several groups to some extent. However, it is not clear at this point if the bulk of the materials in this collection contain examples of his graphics, demonstrate the range of his political activities, reflect a passive interest in various issues and organizations, or a combination of these.
Feminism -- United States; Gay liberation movement; Labor movement -- United States; Prison reformers -- United States; Political parties -- United States; Elections -- Tennessee; Lesbianism -- United States; Homosexuality -- United States; Central America -- Politics and government -- 1979-; United States -- Politics and government -- 20th century; Socialism -- United States; Communism -- United States; Environmental protection -- Citizen participation; Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-1975 -- Protest movements; Black militant organizations -- United States; Black power -- United States; Women's rights -- United States; Civil rights movements -- United States; Nuclear disarmament; World politics; Student movements -- United States; Radicalism -- United States; Guthrie, Milo; Guthrie, Milo; Socialist Party (U.S.)
- Correspondence, 1972-1986, undated 0.2 lin. ft., 3 folders
  Scope and Contents note
  Chiefly incoming letters to Guthrie from members of various organizations concerning support for issues and activities as well as for Socialist Party candidates running in local elections. Arranged chronologically.
  - 1972-1974, 1979-1986, undated, 3 folders (Box 1)
- Campaign Files, 1972-1984. 0.2 lin. ft., 4 folders
  Correspondence, printed materials, and financial papers related to Guthrie's campaign for state representative in Tennessee. Arranged by subject/type of material.
  - Commissioner of Agriculture--Chartam County, 1972 (Box 1)
  - State Representative of Tennessee, 40th District, 1982 (Box 1)
  - State Representative of Tennessee, 40th District, Graphics Work, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Congress, 6th District of Tennessee, 1984 (Box 1)
- Subject Files, 1966-1987. 0.8 lin. ft.
  Articles, newsclippings, and printed materials not associated with a particular organization. Grouped into broad categories of subjects, such as AIDS, nuclear freeze, environment, and racism. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Abortion, 1977, 1984, undated (Box 2)
  - Activists, 1974, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Anarchy, undated (Box 2)
  - Arms Race, 1976, 1980, 1982-1984, undated (Box 2)
  - Central America--general, 1980-1983, undated (Box 2)
  - Central America--Brazil-Honduras, ca. 1980-1986 (Box 2)
  - Central America--Nicaragua, ca. 1982-86 (Box 2)
  - China, ca. 1970 (Box 2)
  - Civil Rights, 1967, 1970-1971, 1973, 1976, 1983, undated (Box 2)
  - Concert Fliers, 1980, undated (Box 2)
  - Death Penalty, undated (Box 2)
  - Draft Resistance, 1981, undated (Box 2)
  - Environment, 1977-1978, 1983, 1985, undated (Box 2)
  - Foat, Margaret, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Guthrie, Milo, 1973,1982 (Box 2)
  - Health, ca. 1973-1986 (Box 2)
  - Homosexual Rights, 1979, 1982-1983, undated (Box 2)
  - Kohl, Helmut, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (Box 2)
  - Law Enforcement Corruption 1972-1973, 1976, 1983, undated (Box 2)
  - Miscellany, undated (Box 2)
  - Native Americans, 1956, 1959, undated (Box 2)
  - Nuclear Power, 1983-1984, undated (Box 2)
  - Peace Movement, ca. 1980-1986 (Box 3)
  - Poverty, 1980, undated (Box 3)
  - Prison/Jail, undated (Box 3)
  - Puerto Rico, ca. 1981 (Box 3)
  - Republican Party, 1981-1983, undated (Box 3)
  - Socialist Theory, ca. 1977-1986 (Box 3)
  - Terrorism, 1982, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Third Parties, ca. 1970-1987 (Box 3)
  - Vietnam, ca. 1966-1972 (Box 3)
  - Violence Against Women, undated (Box 3)
  - Voting, 1980, undated (Box 3)
  - Women's Movement, 1970-1985 (Box 3)
  - Worker's Rights, 1980, undated (Box 3)
- Periodicals, 1962-1987, undated 15 lin. ft.
  Scattered issues from a wide range of liberal to radically left publications. Periodicals includes articles on various political topics as well as news reports of activities. Arranged alphabetically by title of periodical, thereunder numerically (chronologically) by issue/volume number (date).
  - Across Frontiers (World Constitution and Parliament Association), 1985 (Box 4)
  - The Action, 1968 (Box 4)
  - The Activist (Youth Against War and Fascism), 1969-70 (Box 4)
  - Advocate [gay], 1981 (Box 4)
  - The African World, (Youth Organization for Black Unity) 1973 (Box 4)
  - Afro-American Liberator, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Agitator, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Aid Atlanta Newsletter, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Aid League Journal, 1982 (Box 4)
  - AIM (American Independent Movement), 1967 (Box 4)
  - Akwesasne Notes, 1973-1980 (Box 4)
  - Alayaan (Philippine International Community News Service), 1971-1972 (Box 4)
  - Albatross [lesbian satire], 1976 (Box 4)
  - Alfa/Atlanta (Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance), 1973-84 (Box 4)
  - All Africa is Standing Up (Africa Liberation Support Committee), 1978 (Box 4)
  - Alternative (Peace and Freedom Party), 1972-73 (Box 4)
  - Alternative Sources of Energy Magazine, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Amex-Canada (Americans Exiled in Canada), 1975 (Box 4)
  - America, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Anarchist Black Dragon (Washington State Penitentiary), 1981 (Box 4)
  - Appalachia Habitat, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Appalachian Student Press, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Appeal to Reason (Movement Against Racism and the Klan), 1980 (Box 4)
  - Arkansas Gay Writes, (Arkansas Gay Rights, Inc.) 1980 (Box 4)
  - Arm the Spirit (Regional Young Adult Project) [prisoners paper], 1980-81 (Box 4)
  - Asheville Newsletter, 1973 (Box 4)
  - The Atlanta Gay Central (Atlanta Gay Center), 1981 (Box 4)
  - The Atlanta Voice, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Atomic Times, undated (Box 4)
  - Audubon Action [ecology], 1985 (Box 4)
  - The Avator, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Bailly Alliance News [anti-nuclear], 1980 (Box 4)
  - El Barrio, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Battle Acts (Women of Youth Against War and Fascism), 1970 (Box 4)
  - Bay Area Reporter [gay], 1981 (Box 4)
  - Battle Cry, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Bayou La Rose, 1979, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Big Mama Rag [feminist], 1979-81 (Box 4)
  - Bilalian News [black issues], 1976,1978 (Box 4)
  - Black Ink [black liberation], 1969 (Box 4)
  - Black Liberation Month News (Organizing Committee for a New African Liberation Support Committee), 1978 (Box 4)
  - The Black Liberator (Black Liberation Alliance), 1969 (Box 4)
  - The Black Panther (Black Panther Party), 1969-1971 (Box 5)
  - The Black Scholar: Journal of Black Studies and Research, 1983-1984 (Box 5)
  - Blazing Star [gay], 1979 (Box 5)
  - Body Politic [gay liberation], 1979-80, 1984-85 (Box 5)
  - Boletin Internacional (Revolutionary Party of Central American workers), 1982 (Box 6)
  - Boletin Semanal Centroamericano, 1982 (Box 6)
  - The Bond [servicemen's paper], 1969-70 (Box 6)
  - Boston Gay Review, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Boston Sunday Globe, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Bread and Roses [socialist], 1972-76 (Box 6)
  - Breakthrough (Prairie Fire Organizing Committee), 1978 (Box 6)
  - Break the Chain (Sanity Now), 1980 (Box 6)
  - Bring the Troops Home Now Newsletter, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Broadside [feminist], 1979 (Box 6)
  - Brother (National Organization for Changing Men), 1985-86 (Box 6)
  - Bulldozer [prison reform], 1980, 1982 (Box 6)
  - The Burning Spear (African Peoples Socialist Party), 1970-82 (Box 6)
  - Report (Clergy and Laity Concerned), 1981-86 (Box 6)
  - The Call [socialist], 1975-76, 1978, 1980 (Box 6)
  - The California Liberation News, 1974 (Box 6)
  - California Socialist, 1974-75, 1978-80, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Cannon Courier, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Carolina Labor News (AFL-CIO), 1964, 1966-69 (Box 6)
  - The Carolina Plain Dealer, 1972 (Box 6)
  - The Catholic Worker, 1969-70, 1986-87 (Box 6)
  - Central America Alert, 1983-85 (Box 6)
  - Central America Bulletin (Central America Solidarity Association), 1986-87 (Box 6)
  - Challenge (Progressive Labor Party Monthly), 1969 (Box 6)
  - Changing Men, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Chapel Hill Peace Center Newsletter, undated (Box 6)
  - Children of the Green Earth, 1984-85 (Box 6)
  - Christopher Street [gay], 1978 (Box 6)
  - Circle Network News [magic-old religions], 1981 (Box 6)
  - The Citizen's Party Newsletter, 1979 (Box 6)
  - The Citizen's Party Discussion Bulletin, undated (Box 6)
  - Citizen's Voice (Citizen's Party Newspaper) 1981, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Civil Liberties Alert (American Civil Liberties Union), 1984 (Box 6)
  - Class Struggle [communist], 1975 (Box 6)
  - Coalition of Direct Action [newsletter-peace issues], 1985 (Box 6)
  - The Columbus Free Press, 1971, 1980-81 (Box 6)
  - Comin' Out (Project Return), 1985, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Coming Up! [lesbian and gay], 1983-84 (Box 6)
  - Comite de Colorado, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Committee of Returned Volunteers, 1969-70 (Box 6)
  - Common Ground [growth events], 1983 (Box 6)
  - Common Ground Theatre, 1981-82 (Box 6)
  - Common Sense (People's Bicentennial Commission), 1976 (Box 6)
  - The Communist (Worker's Congress), 1975-76 (Box 6)
  - Communities: Journal of Cooperation, 1973, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Community Economic Reporter, 1985-87 (Box 6)
  - Commonweal, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Companero, ca. 1982 (Box 6)
  - Concern Newsletter(Concern for a Free South), 1967 (Box 6)
  - Confrontation [peace issues], 1966 (Box 6)
  - The Connector [peace issues], 1979 (Box 6)
  - Conspiracy, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Consumer Views (Consumer Party), 1979-80 (Box 6)
  - Contra Watch, 1987 (Box 6)
  - CORE-Lator (Congress of Racial Equality), 1964 (Box 6)
  - Corretjer [prison reform paper], undated (Box 6)
  - Counterspy, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Country Activist [farmers/workers solidarity], 1985 (Box 6)
  - Country Women, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Covert Action [issues in Central America], 1983 (Box 6)
  - Critical Mass [energy journal], 1983 (Box 6)
  - The Crusader, 1968 (Box 6)
  - The Daily Californian (University of California at Berkeley), 1969 (Box 7)
  - Daily World [worker solidarity], 1969, 1980, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Dandelion (Movement for a New Society), 1979 (Box 7)
  - Delaware Alternative Press, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Delaware Unlimited [ecological issues], 1985-86 (Box 7)
  - Delivering the Goods, ca. 1967 (Box 7)
  - Democratic Left (Democratic Socialists of America), 1980, 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Democratic Socialist Report and Review, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Determined Action for Women Now (Huron Valley Women's Facility), 1981 (Box 7)
  - Disarming Times, ca. 1984 (Box 7)
  - Distaff [feminist], 1979, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Divide and Conquer (Labor Today), 1977, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Divulgacion Libertaria, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Document: Bulletin of the AAUP at UNC-CH), 1969 (Box 7)
  - Dollars and Sense [economy magazine], 1974-76 (Box 7)
  - Dragon's Blood, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Durham Labor Journal, 1962-63 (Box 7)
  - The Durham Morning Herald, 1969, 1980 (Box 7)
  - The Durham Sun, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Earth First, 1987 (Box 7)
  - El Salvador (Religious Task Force on El Salvador), 1981 (Box 7)
  - El Salvador Alert! (Committee in Solidarity with the People in El Salvador), 1982-83 (Box 7)
  - Elucidation, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Everything for Everybody, 1977 (Box 7)
  - The Existentialist (First Existentialist Church of Atlanta), undated (Box 7)
  - Feminary [lesbian feminist journal], 1979 (Box 7)
  - Fifth Estate, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Fight to Win (Worker-Student Alliance of SDS), 1969 (Box 7)
  - Free Flowing [socialist paper], 1978 (Box 7)
  - Freedom and Dignity [prisoner's paper], undated (Box 7)
  - The Freedom Socialist [feminist paper], 1978-80, 1982-86 (Box 7)
  - Freeze Newsletter (Nashvillians for a Nuclear Arms Freeze), 1984 (Box 7)
  - The Front Page [gay paper], 1979-80, 1982, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Frontline (Line of March), 1986 (Box 7)
  - The Fuse, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Fusion, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Gambit, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Gay and Lesbian Community Voice, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Gay Community News, 1977-83, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Gay Focus, 1981 (Box 8)
  - Gay Life, 1982-83 (Box 8)
  - Gay News, 1980-81 (Box 8)
  - Gay Saskatchewan, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Gay News Telegraph, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Gaysweek, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Gaze [gay paper], 1980, 1982-84, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Gazette [gay paper], 1981 (Box 8)
  - Getting Together, undated (Box 8)
  - GI Press Service, 1969 (Box 8)
  - GI Organizer, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Gidra [Asian-American], 1970 (Box 8)
  - Good News [feminist], 1982 (Box 8)
  - Grass Roots (People's Party),1972-76 (Box 8)
  - Grassroots (People's Party of New Jersey), 1973 (Box 8)
  - Gramma (Central Committee of the Communist Party of Cuba), 1970 (Box 8)
  - The Great Speckled Bird, 1968-70, 1984-85 (Box 8)
  - Green Letter [ecology], 1985 (Box 8)
  - Green Light [ecology], 1985-86 (Box 8)
  - Green Revolution [ecology/decentralism], 1977 (Box 8)
  - The Green Revolution (School of Living), 1973-74 (Box 8)
  - Greensboro Sun, 1973, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Ground Zero [nuclear weapons], 1983-85 (Box 8)
  - The Guardian, 1966-70, 1973-76, 1980-86 (Box 9)
  - Guatemalan Church in Exile, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Guazappa, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Hag Born [feminist], 1979-80 (Box 9)
  - Hapotoc News [prison issues], 1982 (Box 9)
  - Hammer and Tongs (Socialist Party, USA), 1979, 1984-85 (Box 9)
  - Harambee [Afro-American], 1969 (Box 9)
  - Harbinger (International Workers of the World), ca. 1983 (Box 9)
  - Hard Labor [feminist], 1978 (Box 9)
  - Head-On [GI paper], 1969 (Box 9)
  - Highlander Reports, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Hotline [nuclear weapon issues], 1984 (Box 9)
  - The Human Voice (Ann Arbor Human Rights Party) 1984-85 (Box 9)
  - Iceberg! (South-Wide High School), 1969 (Box 10)
  - In These Times, 1977-82, 1984 (Box 10)
  - The Indiana Socialist News, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Indochina Focalpoint, ca. 1973 (Box 10)
  - Industrial Worker, 1970, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Infact News (Infant Formula Action Committee), 1980, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Inquietudes (Spanish language), 1980 (Box 10)
  - Inquiry Magazine, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Institute for Social Ecology, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Intercontinental Press, 1984 (Box 10)
  - International Blacklist, 1983 (Box 10)
  - International Bulletin (Inter-news), 1978 (Box 10)
  - International Labor Defender, 1982 (Box 10)
  - International Socialist Review, 1967, undated (Box 10)
  - Internationalist Worker, 1974-75 (Box 10)
  - The Iowa Idea (Iowa Socialist Party), 1980-85 (Box 10)
  - The James White Review [gay literature journal], 1987 (Box 10)
  - Journal and Guide, 1980 (Box 10)
  - July 4th Bulletin, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Jump Cut [cinema reviews], 1982 (Box 10)
  - The Kudzu (Mississippi Student News Project), 1969 (Box 10)
  - The Kudzu Vine, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Labor News (Socialist Party, USA), 1982 (Box 10)
  - Labor Today, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Lambda (Carolina Gay and Lesbian Association), 1985 (Box 10)
  - Lambda Newsletter [Alabama gay paper], 1980 (Box 10)
  - Lambda Update (Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund), 1984 (Box 10)
  - Lavender Left (Lavender Left Network), 1981, undated (Box 10)
  - The Left Heel (UNC - Chapel Hill chapter of Students for a Democratic Society), 1966 (Box 10)
  - Legal Alliance for Greensboro Justice, 1980s (Box 10)
  - The Lesbian, 1980, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Lesbian Connection, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Lesbian Contradiction, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Let's Work Together [prison paper], 1980 (Box 11)
  - Liberation, 1973, 1976-77 (Box 11)
  - Libertad (National Committee to free Puerto Rican Prisoners of War), 1980-81 (Box 11)
  - The Libertarian Forum, 1980-81 (Box 11)
  - Libertarian Vanguard (Radical Caucus of the Libertarian Party), 1979 (Box 11)
  - Liberty Union (Liberty Union Party), 1974 (Box 11)
  - The Light Journal, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Line of March (Marxist-Leninist journal), 1981 (Box 11)
  - Link [servicemen's journal], 1969 (Box 11)
  - The Lone Star Socialist (Socialist Party of Texas), 1981-82 (Box 11)
  - The Longest Revolution [feminist paper], 1980 (Box 11)
  - Los Angeles Free Press, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Liberation Support Movement News, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Lucha! (Committee in Solidarity with the People in El Salvador), 1980s (Box 11)
  - McCarthy '76, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Maine Land Advocate, 1978-79 (Box 11)
  - Maize [lesbian paper], 1983 (Box 11)
  - El Malcriado (United Farmworkers), 1969, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Mama Bears News and Notes [feminist paper], 1985-86 (Box 11)
  - The March On News [lesbian/gay paper], 1980 (Box 11)
  - Mass Party Organizing Bulletin, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Matchbox (Amnesty International, USA), 1979, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Matchbox (Southern Student Organizing Committee), 1969 (Box 11)
  - May Day! (Journal of Democratic Socialism), 1985 (Box 11)
  - Metropolitan Gazette, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Michigan Free Press, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Midnight Special [prison issues], 1970, ca.1975 (Box 11)
  - The Militant [labor issues], 1965, 1967-1970 (Box 11)
  - The Mill Hunk Herald [labor issues], 1984 (Box 11)
  - Minority Report, 1969 (Box 11)
  - Missing Link (Duke University), 1987 (Box 11)
  - Missouri Valley Socialist, 1981-84 (Box 11)
  - The Mobilizer (Mobilization for Survival), 1980, 1982 (Box 11)
  - Mom...Guess What! [gay paper], 1981 (Box 11)
  - Mom's Apple Pie (Lesbian Mothers' National Defense Fund), 1976-1979 (Box 11)
  - The Monitor (Center for Democratic Renewal), 1986 (Box 11)
  - Monitor (Labor Occupational Health Program), 1976 (Box 11)
  - Moral Majority Report, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Motheroot Journal, 1979-80 (Box 11)
  - Motive [gay], 1972 (Box 11)
  - The Mountain Call, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Mountain Life and Work, 1973-74 (Box 11)
  - Move Over (Citizen's Party), 1980 (Box 11)
  - Movement, 1969-70 (Box 11)
  - Movement (Liberty Union), 1973 (Box 11)
  - The Movement (Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee of California), 1966-69 (Box 11)
  - Muhammad Speaks, 1965, 1970 (Box 11)
  - The Murfreesboro Spotlight, 1984 (Box 11)
  - NACLA Report on the Americas (North American Congress on Latin America), 1980, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Naral News (National Abortion Rights Action League), 1982, 1984-1987 (Box 12)
  - NASC News (Native American Solidarity Committee), undated (Box 12)
  - Nashville Communities Organized for Progress Update, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Nashville News Spectrum, 1983, undated (Box 12)
  - Nashville Report (Clergy and Laity Concerned), 1982-84, 1986, undated (Box 12)
  - The Nation, 1981-82, 1984, 1987 (Box 12)
  - National Conservative Political Action Committee Conservative Action Report, 1981 (Box 12)
  - The National Lawyers Guild Practitioner, 1967 (Box 12)
  - National Newsletter (US-China Peoples Friendship Association), 1975 (Box 12)
  - New America, 1969-70 (Box 12)
  - New American Movement, 1973-74, undated (Box 12)
  - A New Day, 1980 (Box 12)
  - The New Day, undated (Box 12)
  - New Directions For Women, 1980-81, 1983 (Box 12)
  - New Movement in Solidarity with Puerto Rican Independence Bulletin, 1979-80, undated (Box 12)
  - New Mobilizer (New Mobilization Committee to end the War in Vietnam), 1969 (Box 12)
  - New Options, 1985-87 (Box 12)
  - New Salute, 1969 (Box 12)
  - New Solidarity (National Caucus of Labor Committees and the US Labor Party), 1975-76 (Box 12)
  - The New South Student, 1966-69 (Box 12)
  - New Unity, 1973 (Box 12)
  - New Wilderness Letter, 1977 (Box 12)
  - New Women's Times, 1979-80, 1982 (Box 12)
  - The New York Alliance, 1983-84 (Box 12)
  - The New York Herald Tribune, undated (Box 12)
  - New York High School Free Press, undated (Box 12)
  - New York Native, 1982 (Box 12)
  - New York Times Magazine, 1978 (Box 12)
  - The News, 1986 (Box 12)
  - News and Letters, 1983 (Box 12)
  - News and Views of the Federation For Progress, 1983 (Box 12)
  - News Notes (Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors), 1967 (Box 12)
  - A Newsletter (Nashville Women's Alliance), 1980-82, 1984-85 (Box 12)
  - Newsletter (North Carolina Political Prisoner Committee), 1973 (Box 12)
  - Newsletter and Strike Bulletin (Student Mobilization Committee to end the War in Vietnam), 1968 (Box 12)
  - NIC Bulletin (National Interim Committee for a Mass Party), 1974-75 (Box 12)
  - Nicaragua (National Network in Solidarity with the Nicaraguan People), 1982 (Box 12)
  - Nicwomen, 1975 (Box 12)
  - No Nuclear News, 1984 (Box 12)
  - The Non-Violent Activist ( War Resisters League), 1985-87 (Box 12)
  - North American Anarchist, 1979-80 (Box 12)
  - North American Farmer, 1984 (Box 12)
  - North Carolina Civil Liberties News, 1968/69 (Box 12)
  - The North Carolina Independent, 1983-85 (Box 12)
  - North Carolinians Against Racist and Religious Violence Newsletter, 1985 (Box 13)
  - North Country Anvil, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Northern Sun, 1983 (Box 13)
  - The Northwest Call (Socialist Party, USA), ca.1980 (Box 13)
  - Not Far Enough (Democratic Socialists of America Feminist Commission), 1983 (Box 13)
  - Not Man Apart (Friends of Earth League of Conservation Voters), 1974-75 (Box 13)
  - Now! News (National Welfare Rights Organization), 1969 (Box 13)